{
    "id": "e0b4d31b6a5b481089ef2716a0747dff",
    "title": "Prepositions By, With, To",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a7384317321a4395b445cc780361698b",
            "title": "Prepositions By, With, To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She was red ……………………….. embarrassment.",
                    "description": "With is used in a number of expressions which show how people are showing their emotions and sensations. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "by",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The travelers were shivering ……………………. cold.",
                    "description": "With is used in a number of expressions which show how people are showing their emotions and sensations. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "by",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I drew their attention ………………………. shouting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "by",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You should reach there ………………………. 5 o’clock.",
                    "description": "By can mean not later than.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "by",
                        "within"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………… the end of the party, everybody was tired.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "By",
                        "With",
                        "To"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He succeeded ……………………… hard work.",
                    "description": "We use by to talk about what we do to get a certain result. We use with to talk about what we use to get a result. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "by",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our roof was damaged ………………………. the storm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "with",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was interrogated ……………………….. the police inspector.",
                    "description": "In passive voice, by is used to introduce the agent.",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "to",
                        "by"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He earned just enough to get ……………………….",
                    "description": "To get by is to survive with great difficulty.",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "with",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please be patient …………………….. the children.",
                    "description": "With is used after several adjectives which show how people are feeling towards others.",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "with",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has always been nice …………………….. me.",
                    "description": "With is not used with words like kind, polite, nice, rude etc. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "with",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There are so many people ……………………….. no homes.",
                    "description": "With indicates possession. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "by",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}